

CONTACT

me@nolanalbert.com
www.nolanalbert.com
www.linkedin.com/in/nolalb

PROFILE

I am a hard-working Information Technology professional with a passion for new and evolving technology. I take great pride in the work that I do and stand behind my delivered products. My passion for technology and the pride I take in my work are evident both in and outside of the office.

I have strong experience in healthcare IT with a focus on interoperability, as well as client support. This experience combined with my passion for the field enables me to provide thoughtful and effective solutions.

SKILLS

- HL7 INTERFACING
- EDI STANDARDS
- MIRTH
- CLOVERLEAF
- MEDITECH C/S
- CCD
- SOL
- SSRS

EDUCATION

Certified Cloverleaf Level 2 Developer

Mar. 2023

Cybersecurity B.S.

SUNY Alfred State 2016-2020

EXPERIENCE

Senior Interface Analyst | The CBORD Group

Feb. 2024-Present

I'd love to talk with you about my work at CBORD! Please reach out for the details of my current position

Enterprise Data Analyst | Upper Allegheny Health System

May 2022-Feb. 2024

Responsible for all HL7 interfacing within the health system Including troubleshooting, after-hours support, new implementations, and maintenance.

Administered SQL Server Databases, SQL Server Reporting Services, and SQL Server Integration Services. Including: Upgrading and migrating these to new VMs.

Created SQL queries and reports utilizing SQL Server Reporting Services to fulfill organizational goals. Such as: Building a report to calculate the NEDOCS.

Led high-impact projects that enhanced the health system's ability to serve its patients. For example: Moving Meditech CCDs to the MU3 format

Responsible for SharePoint administration and design.

Enterprise Data Specialist | Upper Allegheny Health System

Oct. 2021-May 2022

Monitored and maintained HL7 interfaces in Cloverleaf.

Wrote SQL queries to create reports in SSRS utilizing data from the Meditech EHR.

Created Meditech NPR reports and macros for reporting on data not available in SQL.

Modernized the department's automated file transfers system.

Utilized ServiceNow to document issues and requests in detail.